让我们继续努力
Let's continue working on
我们非常小的鞋品项目，
our very small shoe article project,
在这个编码挑战第二。
in this coding challenge number two.
所以就像以前一样，使用结果
So just like before, use the results
之前的挑战
of the previous challenge
作为这一点的起点。
as the starting point for this one.
如果由于某种原因你没有那个代码，
And if for some reason you don't have that code,
那么一如既往，
then as always,
我有启动器和最终代码链接
I have the starter and the final code links
在这个讲座的某个地方，但当然会更好，
somewhere in this lecture, but it would be better of course,
如果您要使用自己的代码，
if you would use your own code,
也许如果你在 CodePen 上有它，
maybe if you have it on CodePen,
或者如果你在自己的电脑上做这个挑战
or if you're doing this challenge on your own computer
使用VSCode，好吗？
using VSCode, all right?
所以，我们最终得到了这个结果
So, we ended up with this result
在最后的编码挑战中。
in the last coding challenge.
所以记得是这个，
So remember it was this,
而我现在想让你做的就是利用你的新知识
and what I want you to do now is to use your new knowledge
关于盒子模型得出这个结果。
about the box model to arrive at this result.
所以你在这里看到这篇文章，
So you see that this article here,
所以这个元素现在窄了很多，
so this element is a lot more narrow now,
它也很好地位于页面中心。
and it is also nicely centered in the page.
所以这里这个容器的宽度，
So the width of this container here,
所以这篇文章元素是825像素。
so this article element is 825 pixels.
接下来，您可以看到许多边距和填充
Next, you can see that many margins and paddings
已被删除，因此这可能意味着
have been removed and so that probably means
这里有一些全局重置。
that there has been some global reset here.
就像我们在其中一场讲座中所做的那样，
So do that just like we did in one of the lectures,
但是当然要继续添加一些填充
but then of course keep adding back some paddings
和一些利润。
and some margins.
所以每当你在这个例子中看到一些空间时，
So whenever you see some space here in this example,
例如，在这里，在这个标题的内部，
for example, here, inside of this heading,
那么当然你需要添加一些空间
then of course you need to add back some space
如您所知，您可以使用边距或填充来做到这一点，
and you can do that using margin or padding as you know,
所以只要选择适合情况的写一个
so just choose the write one for the right situation
或根据你所学的。
or according to what you learned.
最后，还有一点就是
Finally, another thing is that
这个按钮现在很宽，
this button here now is a really wide,
所以它一直跨越
so it spans all the way
从左边到右边，
from the left side to the right side,
而且它现在在顶部有这个边界
and also it now has this border here at the top
所以要创造一个按钮的错觉
so to create this illusion of a button
即使我们悬停在它上面。
even when we're hovering it.
所以看看你能不能得出这个结果，
So see if you can maybe arrive at this result,
但如果你不能，那当然是，
but if you can't then that's of course,
一如既往不是大问题。
as always not a big problem.
所以现在就花点时间真正尝试一下
So just take some time now and really try
编码这个挑战，我看到你回到这里
to code up this challenge and I see you back here
当你完成时。
when you are done.
好的。
Okay.
因此，让我们不要浪费时间，立即开始。
So let's waste no time and start right away.
我将真正开始，
And I will actually start,
在这里给我们更多的空间。
give us some more space here.
所以我将从我提到的全局重置开始，
So I will start with that global reset I mentioned,
所以添加零边距和零填充
so adding a margin of zero and a padding of zero
到页面上的每个元素。
to every single element on the page.
好的。
All right.
现在我将在这里实际制作这个产品，
And now I will actually make this product here,
所以这个元素，我会给它的宽度
so this element, I will give it to the width of
正如我之前提到的，825 像素。
825 pixels as I had mentioned before.
好的。
All right.
所以现在是时候把它放在浏览器中了。
And so now it's time to center this in the browser.
而在最后一堂课中，
And in the last lecture,
我实际上向您展示了如何做到这一点。
I actually showed you how to do that.
所以在那里，我们创建了一个我们称之为的元素
So there, we created an element that we called
容器，然后我们将它放在身体内部。
the container, and then we centered that inside of the body.
现在，在这种情况下，容器基本上是
Now, in this case, the container is basically
这个产品在这里，对吧？
this product here, right?
这就是我们添加宽度的地方
And so that is where we add the width
这也是我们现在设置的地方
and so that's where we also set now
左边距和右边距为自动。
the left and right margins to auto.
所以我在这里使用速记并给出它
So I'm using the shorthand here and giving it
在顶部和底部，零
at the top and the bottom, zero
然后左右，自动。
and then left and right, auto.
所以，我们开始吧。
And so, here we go.
现在它在身体内部居中。
Now it is centered inside of the body.
很漂亮，但我们实际上可以做得更好一点
Beautiful, but we can actually make this a bit better
因为现在它有点粘在上面
because now it's kind of glued to the top here
和这里一样。
and the same down here.
所以不是让顶部和底部都为零，
So instead of having top and bottom at zero,
让我们将它们设置为 50 像素。
let's set them to 50 pixels.
所以，这基本上创造了一些空间
And so, that then creates some space basically
围绕这个元素。
around this element.
所以我们在这里添加了 50 个，在下面添加了 50 个，在顶部添加了 50 个。
So we added 50 here, down here, and 50 here at the top.
伟大的。
Great.
接下来，让我们在标题中添加一些空格，
Next, let's add some space back here in the heading,
这就是产品标题。
so that is the product title.
所以，现在我们想要元素内部的一些空间
And so, now we want some space inside of the element
这样我们就可以在这里创建一些空白空间，
so that we can create some empty space here,
它仍然有一些背景颜色。
which still has some background color.
对？
Right?
所以这就是我们使用填充的原因，因为我们想要
So that's why we use padding because we want
该空间位于元素内部
that space to be inside of the element
而不是在它之外。
and not outside of it.
所以如果它是一个利润，
So if it was a margin,
那么它看起来像这样
then it would look like this
然后背景颜色当然会
and then the background color would of course
不在这里的任何地方。
not be anywhere here.
所以因为它在外面，对，我们想要里面
So because it's outside, right, we wanted inside
所以这就是填充。
and so then that's padding.
好的。
All right.
所以这开始看起来好多了。
So that's starting to look a lot better.
现在也许让我们在这里创造一些空间
Now maybe let's create some space here
在此运输和此文本之间。
between this shipping and this text.
因此，为了创造一些垂直空间，
And so for that, so for creating some vertical space,
我再次使用边距底部。
I am again using margin bottom.
所以在这里运输，让我们添加
So here in shipping, let's add
一些
some
利润
margin
底部
bottom
比方说，20 像素。
of, let's say, 20 pixels.
是的，看起来好多了
Yeah, that looks a lot better
让我们看看最终的结果
and let's take a look at the final result
我们想要达到的目标。
that we want to achieve.
所以你看我们这里也有一些空间。
And so you see we have some space here as well.
我们在此标题下方也有一些空间，
We also have some space below this heading here,
然后这个无序列表也移回了
and then this unordered list also moved back
在容器内部，
here inside of the container,
因为请注意，现在，这些子弹在外面。
because notice that right now, these bullets are outside.
对？
Right?
所以我们不要解决所有这些问题。
And so let's not fix all of that.
所以让我们从这里开始
So let's start with this one here
并像往常一样给它15个像素，
and giving it 15 pixels and as always,
如果你这里的数字不同
if your numbers here were different
那么这根本不重要。
then that doesn't matter at all.
好的。
All right.
现在这个链接和这个标题之间有一些空间，
And now some space here between this link and this title,
所以这个标题和合乎逻辑的事情
so this heading and the logical thing to do
可能是在链接底部添加一些边距，
would probably be to add some margin bottom to the link,
因为正如我所说，
because as I said,
最好的办法是坚持其中一个方向，
the best thing to do is to stick to one of the directions,
所以到一侧，然后总是在那里添加边距。
so to one of the sides and then always add the margin there.
所以让我们试试吧。
So let's try that.
所以这是更多信息链接，
So it's this more info link,
但你会发现这实际上是行不通的。
but you will see that this will actually not work.
所以你看我们添加了它但它不起作用。
So you see we added it and it doesn't work.
以及它不起作用的原因
And the reason why it doesn't work
是我将在下一课中解释的内容。
is something that I will explain in the next lecture.
好的。
All right.
所以现在重要的是这行不通
So what matters now is that this doesn't work
因为你基本凯莉不能使用边距
because you basically cannot use margins
在像锚这样的小元素上，所以喜欢这个链接。
on small elements like anchors, so like this link.
所以相反，我们现在要做的
And so instead, what we will do now
是在顶部添加边距
is to add a margin to the top
这个元素的。
of this element.
因此，这将在视觉上看起来完全相同。
And so this will then visually look exactly the same way.
对，所以在底部加上 30，
Right, so adding 30 to the bottom of this,
它看起来与添加 30 基本相同
it looks essentially the same as adding 30
到这个的顶部。
to the top of this one.
接下来，让我们修复
Next, let's then fix
这些不属于我们的要点
these bullet points that are outside of our
容器元素。
container element.
所以左边距，比方说20像素。
So margin left, let's say 20 pixels.
是的，所以看起来不错。
Yeah, so that looks nice.
现在我也想在这里添加一些空间
And now I want to add some space here also
这些元素之间。
between these elements.
这就是这里的详细信息列表，
So that is this details list right here,
所以让我们选择这些元素中的每一个
and so let's select each of these elements
在那里。
that are in there.
所以 .details-list
So .details-list
然后是所有 li 子元素
and then all the li child elements
所以这里是一个后代选择器，
So this right here is a descendant selector,
就像我们之前学到的一样
just like we have learned previously
正如我们以前多次使用过的那样。
and as we have used many times before.
我想我们从未使用过它
I think we have never used it
其中一个是这样的类选择器
where one of them is a class selector like this
另一个是元素，
and the other is an element,
但这当然没问题。
but of course that's no problem.
我们可以以任何我们想要的方式组合它们。
We can just combine them in any way that we want.
现在让我们添加那个空间，
And so let's now add that space,
比方说大约10个像素。
let's say some 10 pixels.
现在终于要结束了，
And now finally to finish,
让我们在这个按钮上做一点工作。
let's work a little bit here on this button.
所以这个，我将从这里的一些填充开始。
So this one, and I'm going to start with some padding here.
所以在按钮内部添加一些空间。
So adding some space inside of the button.
这样看起来已经好多了，对吧？
So that already looks a lot nicer, right?
但现在让我们从一侧开始
But now let's have it go from one side
一直到另一边。
all the way to the other side.
所以这与我们对图像所做的非常相似
So that's something very similar as we did with the image
在之前的一次讲座中。
in one of the previous lectures.
所以我们可以简单地给它一个 100% 的宽度。
So we can simply give it a width of 100%.
所以现在它基本上占据了整个父元素，
And so now it basically occupies the entire parent element,
这当然是完整的文章元素。
which is of course this complete article element.
现在我们所缺少的只是顶部的边框。
And now all that we are missing is that border at the top.
对，所以请记住，在我们的演示中，当我们将其悬停时，
Right, so remember that here in our demo, when we hover it,
然后它仍然有点像一个按钮，对，
then it still kind of looks like a button, right,
为了创造这种效果，
and in order to create that effect,
所以那种错觉，
so that kind of illusion,
我们在按钮顶部需要这个边框。
we need this border here at the top of the button.
所以让我们添加
So let's add that
和
and
所以它基本上是相同的边界
so it is basically the same border
就像这篇文章一样。
as goes around this article.
所以让我们看看我们有什么
So let's see what we have there
我们实际上可以继续复制它。
and we can actually go ahead and copy it.
我们唯一需要改变的就是
The only thing that we need to then change
是我们只希望这个边框在顶部，在这种情况下。
is that we only want this border at the top, in this case.
好的，现在我们开始。
Okay, and now there we go.
太漂亮了，效果很好。
So beautiful, that works just nice.
我认为有了这个，我们实际上完成了这个挑战。
And I think with this, we actually finished this challenge.
所以它看起来就像，我们的演示在这里。
So it looks just like, our demo here.
所以我认为我们已经完成了这个挑战。
So I think we're done here with this challenge.
干得好，干得好，祝贺你
So great job, well done and congratulations
再次自己编写大量代码。
for writing a lot of code on your own once again.
所以这些对你来说真的非常重要
So these are really, really important for you to
巩固你的知识。
consolidate your knowledge.
所以我很高兴看到
So I'm very happy to see
在这一点上你仍然和我在一起，
that you're still with me here at this point,
因为那真的很棒p进步。
because that's really great progress.